eventshigh.com 2019-01-01

# PRIVACY POLICY

                                 PRIVACY POLICY
We, Njuta Technologies Pvt Ltd, a Private Limited Company incorporate under the
Indian Companies Act, 2013 (hereinafter referred to as “Company”), having its
registered office at AMR Tech Park-1, First Floor, IT Industry Nagarathpura, Hosur
Road Bangalore Karnataka 560068 India , the creator of this Privacy Policy ensure our
firm commitment to your privacy vis-à-vis the protection of your priceless information.
In order to endow you with our uninterrupted use of services, we may collect and, in
some circumstances, disclose information about you. To enhance better protection of
your privacy we provide this notice explaining our information practices and the choices
you can make about the way your information is collected and used.
All visitors to our website and mobile Application are advised to read and understand
our Privacy Policy carefully, as by accessing the Website and mobile Application you
agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of the Privacy Policy and consent to the
collection, storage and use of information relating to you as provided herein.
If you do not agree with the terms and conditions of our Privacy Policy, including in
relation to the manner of collection or use of your information, please do not use or
access the Site.
If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, you should contact
our Customer Support Desk at support@eventshigh.com
ANY CAPITALIZED WORDS USED HENCEFORTH SHALL HAVE THE MEANING
ACCORDED TO THEM UNDER THIS AGREEMENT. FURTHER, ALL HEADING
USED HEREIN ARE ONLY FOR THE PURPOSE OF ARRANGING THE VARIOUS
PROVISIONS OF THE AGREEMENT IN ANY MANNER. NEITHER THE USER NOR
THE CREATERS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY MAY USE THE HEADING TO
INTERPRET THE PROVISIONS CONTAINED WITHIN IT IN ANY MANNER.
1. DEFINITIONS:
a. “We”, “Our”, and “Us” shall mean and refer to the creators of this privacy policy.

b. “You”, “Your”, “Yourself” and “User” shall mean and refer to natural and legal
   individuals who use the Website.
c. “Website” shall mean and refer to www.eventshigh.com owned and operated by the
   Company.
d. “Website” shall mean the website EventsHigh.
e. “Personal Information” shall mean and refer to any personally identifiable
   information that We may collect from You. For removal of any doubts, please refer to
   Clause 2.
2. OVERVIEW
   We commit to respecting your online privacy data. We further recognize your need
   for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable
   information ("Personal Information") you share with us. Information that is
   considered personal about you by us includes, but is not limited to, your name,
   address, email address, phone number or other contact information.
   In order to avail any services through the Website, you are required to provide the
   following information which includes, but is not limited to:
   •   Name;
   •   Age;
   •   Sex;
   •   User name;
   •   Password;
   •   Address;
   •   Mobile number;
   •   Interests;
   •   E-mail address; and
   •   Payment details such as Debit/Credit card details.

   This privacy policy also applies to data we collect from users who are not registered
   as members of this site, including, but not limited to, browsing behaviour, pages
   viewed etc.
3. NOTIFICATION         OF    MODIFICATIONS       AND   CHANGES       TO THE      T&C     AND
   PRIVACY POLICY
   We reserve the right to change the Terms and Privacy Policy from time to time as we
   deem fit, without any intimation to you, and your continued use of the site will
   signify your acceptance of any amendment to these terms.
   You are therefore advised to re-read the Terms of Service on a regular basis. Should
   it be that you do not accept any of the modifications or amendments to the Terms,
   you may terminate your use of this Website/Application immediately.
4. INFORMATION WE COLLECT
   Our Website/ Application requires users to give us contact information (like your name,
   address, telephone number and email address), and demographic information (like your zip
   code/pin code). As a member, you are required to provide a valid email address at
   registration and this email address maybe your username and it will represent your identity
   on our Website/Application. This information is compiled and analysed on an aggregated
   basis. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is
   on the Site or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on the Site or not), your
   computer browser information, your IP address, and other information associated with your
   interaction with the Site.
   We also collect and store personal information provided by you from time to time on
   the Site. We only collect and use such information from you that we consider
   necessary for achieving a seamless, efficient and safe experience, customized to your
   needs including:
   •   To enable the provision of services opted for by you;
   •   To communicate necessary account and service related information from time to
       time;

•   To allow you to receive quality customer care services;
•   To undertake necessary fraud and money laundering prevention checks, and
    comply with the highest security standards;
•   To comply with applicable laws, rules and regulations; and
•   To provide you with information and offers on services, on updates, on
    promotions, on related, affiliated or associated service providers and partners
    that we believe would be of interest to you.
Where any service requested by you involves a third party, such information as is
reasonably necessary by the Company to carry out your service request may be
shared with such third party.
We may use your contact information to send you offers based on your interests and
prior activity. The Company may also use contact information internally to direct its
efforts for service improvement, to contact you as a survey respondent, to notify you
if you win any contest; and to send you promotional materials from its contest
sponsors or advertisers.
We collect and store your search details on the Website/Application, including your
search history, the usage of the Website/Application and the features and time you
have used the Website/Application for. We collect any communications between you
and other users or third parties through our Website/Application and details of any
external links that you click on.
Further, you may from time to time choose to provide payment related financial
information (credit card, debit card, bank account details, billing address etc.) on the
Website/Application.     We    are   committed    to   keeping    all  such    sensitive
data/information safe at all times and ensure that such data/information is only
transacted over secure Site of approved payment gateways which are digitally
encrypted, and provide the highest possible degree of care available under the

   technology                      presently                     in                  use.
   The Company will not use your financial information for any purpose other than to
   complete a transaction with you.
   To the extent possible, we provide you the option of not divulging any specific
   information that you wish for us not to collect, store or use. You may also choose not
   to use a particular service or feature on the Site, and opt out of any non-essential
   communications from the Company.
   Further, transacting over the internet has inherent risks which can only be avoided
   by you following security practices yourself, such as not revealing account/login
   related information to any other person and informing our customer care team about
   any suspicious activity or where your account has/may have been compromised.
5. HOW INFORMATION IS COLLECTED
   a. Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the
       purposes for which information is being collected.
   b. We will collect and use your personal information solely with the objective of
       fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes,
       unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
   c. We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfilment of
       those purposes.
   d. We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where
       appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
   e. Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to
       the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-
       date.
6. COOKIES
   a. We use data collection devices such as "cookies" on certain pages of our
       Website/Application. "Cookies" are small files sited on your hard drive that assist

       us in providing customized services. We also offer certain features that are only
       available through the use of a "cookie". Cookies can also help us provide
       information, which is targeted to your interests. Cookies may be used to identify
       logged in or registered users.
   b. Third party vendors including www.google.com (“Google”) may use cookies to
       serve ads based on your visits to this Website/Application. You may visit the
       Website/Application of the third party and choose to opt out of the use of cookies
       for interest-based advertising, if the third party offers such an option. You may
       choose to opt-out of the DoubleClick cookie that Google and its partners use for
       interest-based advertising by visiting Ads Settings.
   c. The Website/Application also has enabled the Google Analytics Advertising,
       which allows Google to collect data about users on our Website/Application, in
       addition to Google advertising cookies and anonymous identifiers. You may
       choose to opt out of this by downloading and installing the Google Analytics opt-
       out add-on here https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/.
7. EXTERNAL LINKS ON WEBSITE
   The Website/Application may include hyperlinks to other web sites or content or
   resources. We have no control over any websites or resources, which are provided by
   companies or persons other than Us.
   You acknowledge and agree that We are not responsible for the availability of any
   such external sites or resources, and does not endorse any advertising,
   services/products or other materials on or available from such websites or resources.
   You acknowledge and agree that We are not liable for any loss or damage which may
   be incurred by you as a result of the availability of those external sites or resources,
   or as a result of any reliance placed by you on the completeness, accuracy or
   existence of any advertising, products or other materials on, or available from, such
   websites or resources. These third-party service providers and Third-Party Sites may
   have their own privacy policies governing the storage and retention of your personal
   information that you may be subject to. We recommend that when you enter a Third-

   Party Site, you review the Third Party Site’s privacy policy as it relates to
   safeguarding your personal information.
8. OUR USE OF YOUR INFORMATION
   Your contact information is used to contact you when necessary. We use your IP
   address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our
   Website/Application and Mobile Website. Your IP address is also used to help
   identify you and to gather broad demographic information. Finally, we may use your
   IP address to help protect our partners and ourselves from fraud. We will continue to
   enhance our security procedures as new technology becomes available. We will
   transfer information about you if We are acquired by or merged with another
   company. In this event, we will notify you by email or by putting a prominent notice
   on the site before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a
   different privacy policy.
   We may release your personal information to a third-party in order to comply with a
   Court Order or other similar legal procedure, or when we believe in good faith that
   such disclosure is necessary to comply with the law; prevent imminent physical harm
   or financial loss; or investigate or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected
   fraud, or violations of Our Terms of Use. We may disclose personally identifiable
   information to parties in compliance with our Copyright Policy as mentioned in
   the Terms of Use as we in our sole discretion believe necessary or appropriate in
   connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy,
   or other unlawful activity. In such events, We may disclose name, address, country,
   phone number, email address and company name.
9. CONFIDENTIALITY
   You further acknowledge that the Website/Application may contain information
   which is designated confidential by Us and that you shall not disclose such
   information without our prior written consent.
   Your information is regarded as confidential and therefore will not be divulged to
   any third party, unless if legally required to do so to the appropriate authorities.

  We will not sell, share, or rent your personal information to any third party or use
  your e-mail address for unsolicited mail. Any emails sent by us will only be in
  connection with the provision of agreed services.
10.    OUR DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION
    Due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your
    private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be
    disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example
    (without limiting and foregoing), we may be forced to disclose information to the
    government,      law   enforcement   agencies   or  third    parties.   Under    certain
    circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or
    private communications, or members may abuse or misuse your information that
    they collect from our Website/Application. Therefore, although we use industry
    standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not
    expect, that your personally identifiable information or private communications
    would always remain private.
    As a matter of policy, we do not sell or rent any personally identifiable information
    about you to any third party. However, the following describes some of the ways
    that your personally identifiable information may be disclosed:
    a. External Service Providers: There may be a number of services offered by
        external service providers that help you use our Website/Applications. If you
        choose to use these optional services, and in the course of doing so, disclose
        information to the external service providers, and/or grant them permission to
        collect information about you, then their use of your information is governed by
        their private policy.
    b. Other Corporate Entities: We share much of our data, including personally
        identifiable information about you, with our parent and/or subsidiaries that are
        committed to serving your online needs and related services, throughout the
        world. Such data will be shared for the sole purpose of enhancing your browsing
        experience and providing our services to you. To the extent that these entities
        have access to your information, they will treat it at least as protectively as they

       treat information they obtain from their other members. It is possible that We
       and/or its subsidiaries, or any combination of such, could merge with or be
       acquired by another business entity. Should such a combination occur, you
       should expect that we would share some or all of your information in order to
       continue to provide the service. You will receive notice of such event (to the
       extent that it occurs).
       Law and Order: We cooperate with law enforcement inquiries, as well as other
       third parties to enforce laws, such as: intellectual property rights, fraud and
       other rights. We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about
       you to law enforcement and other government officials as we, in our sole
       discretion, believe necessary or appropriate, in connection with an investigation
       of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or
       may expose us or you to legal liability.
11.    ACCESSING AND REVIEWING INFORMATION
   Following registration, you can review and change the information you submitted. If
   you change any information we may or may not keep track of your old information.
   You can change your registration information such as: name, phone number, and
   other profile information.
   We will retain in our files information you have requested to remove for certain
   circumstances, such as to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our
   terms and conditions. Further, such prior information is never completely removed
   from our databases due to technical and legal constraints, including stored 'back up'
   systems. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your personally identifiable
   information will be completely removed from our databases in response to your
   requests.
12.    CONTROL OF YOUR PASSWORD
   When you sign up to become a Member, you will also be asked to choose a password.
   You are entirely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password. It
   is important that you protect it against unauthorized access of your account and

   information by choosing your password carefully, and keeping your password and
   computer secure by signing out after using our services.
    You agree not to use the account, username, email address or password of another
   Member at any time or to disclose your password to any third party. If you choose to
   share this information with third parties to provide you additional services, you are
   responsible for all actions taken with your login information and password and
   therefore should review each third party's privacy policy. You are responsible for all
   actions taken with your login information and password, including fees. If you lose
   control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personally
   identifiable information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your
   behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you
   should immediately change your password. You agree to notify us immediately if you
   suspect any consistent unauthorized use of your account or access to your password
   even after changing it.
13.    OTHER INFORMATION COLLECTORS
   Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document only
   addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent
   that you disclose your information to other parties, whether they are on our
   Website/Application or on other sites throughout the Internet, different rules may
   apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. To the extent
   that we use third party advertisers, they adhere to their own privacy policies. Since
   we do not control the privacy policies of the third parties, you are subject to ask
   questions before you disclose your personal information to others.
14.    SECURITY
   We treat data as an asset that must be protected against loss and unauthorized
   access. We employ many different security techniques to protect such data from
   unauthorized access by members inside and outside the company. We do not
   recommend transfer of sensitive information (such as credit card number) and bank
   account details via the Site and mobile Applicationto other Users. Users are

   recommended to do so offline, on the phone or via personal emails. We follow
   generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted
   to us, both during transmission and once We receive it. However, "perfect security"
   does not exist on the Internet. You therefore agree that any security breaches beyond
   the control of our standard security procedures are at your sole risk and discretion.
15.    DISCLAIMER
   We cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personal
   information (including sensitive information like credit card information and bank
   account number) will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this
   Privacy Policy. Therefore, although we are committed to protecting your privacy, we
   do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information will
   always remain private. As a user of the Site, you understand and agree that you
   assume all responsibility and risk for your use of the Site and mobile
   Website/Application, the internet generally, and the documents you post or access
   and for your conduct on and off the Site.
 16. QUESTIONS AND SUGGESTIONS
   If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, you should
   contact us by sending an email to hello@eventshigh.com
 17. GRIEVANCE OFFICER
     In accordance with Information Technology Act 2000 and rules made there under,
     the name and contact details of the Grievance Officer is provided below:
       Arvind Batra, Director Njuta Technologies Pvt. Ltd.
     hello@eventshigh.com
